{
  "multiplication": [
    {
      "prompt": "68 x 50",
      "optionA": "3000",
      "optionB": "3400",
      "optionC": "5000",
      "optionD": "7000",
      "answer": "3400"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "23 x 77",
      "optionA": "1771",
      "optionB": "7000",
      "optionC": "4536",
      "optionD": "6546",
      "answer": "1771"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "55 x 55",
      "optionA": "5555",
      "optionB": "1234",
      "optionC": "",
      "optionD": "3025",
      "answer": "3025"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "6 x 9",
      "optionA": "54",
      "optionB": "45",
      "optionC": "96",
      "optionD": "69",
      "answer": "54"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "99 x 0",
      "optionA": "990",
      "optionB": "0",
      "optionC": "909",
      "optionD": "99",
      "answer": "0"
    }
  ],
  "subtraction": [
    {
      "prompt": "1001 - 289",
      "optionA": "712",
      "optionB": "211",
      "optionC": "Error",
      "optionD": "799",
      "answer": "712"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "960 - 986",
      "optionA": "10",
      "optionB": "-9",
      "optionC": "-26",
      "optionD": "88",
      "answer": "-26"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "700 - 100",
      "optionA": "70",
      "optionB": "10",
      "optionC": "600",
      "optionD": "1000",
      "answer": "600"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "2000 - 101",
      "optionA": "888",
      "optionB": "1899",
      "optionC": "797",
      "optionD": "1909",
      "answer": "1899"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "888 - 99",
      "optionA": "566",
      "optionB": "987",
      "optionC": "555",
      "optionD": "789",
      "answer": "789"
    }
  ],
  "addition": [
    {
      "prompt": "20 + 50",
      "optionA": "2070",
      "optionB": "07",
      "optionC": "5020",
      "optionD": "70",
      "answer": "70"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "100 + 101",
      "optionA": "101100",
      "optionB": "603",
      "optionC": "202",
      "optionD": "100101",
      "answer": "202"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "400 + 600",
      "optionA": "1000",
      "optionB": "200",
      "optionC": "6040",
      "optionD": "046",
      "answer": "1000"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "300  + 999",
      "optionA": "1290",
      "optionB": "444",
      "optionC": "909",
      "optionD": "665",
      "answer": "1290"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "499 + 1",
      "optionA": "491",
      "optionB": "499",
      "optionC": "500",
      "optionD": "4991",
      "answer": "500"
    }
  ],
  "division": [
    {
      "prompt": "400 / 8",
      "optionA": "60",
      "optionB": "58",
      "optionC": "50",
      "optionD": "48",
      "answer": "50"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "600 / 100",
      "optionA": "10",
      "optionB": "60",
      "optionC": "6",
      "optionD": "7",
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "999 / 3",
      "optionA": "99",
      "optionB": "677",
      "optionC": "543",
      "optionD": "333",
      "answer": "333"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "1001 / 7",
      "optionA": "143",
      "optionB": "76",
      "optionC": "90",
      "optionD": "56",
      "answer": "143"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "660 / 11",
      "optionA": "66",
      "optionB": "55",
      "optionC": "60",
      "optionD": "55",
      "answer": "60"
    }
  ]
}
